Finding Aid for the CBS Inc. Film and Television Collection PASC-M.0072
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Television Programs, Series 4.
  - Gunsmoke -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 62.
    - Comanches is Soft, 1964; open reel tape (Box 3099, Box 1103, Folder 1)
      On container, "W. Hatch."
    - Cotter's Girl, 1962 December 19; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1143, Folder 7)
      On container, "Gunsmoke #31219/"Cotter's Girl"."
    - Don Matteo, 1960 July 26; open reel tape (Box 1103, Folder 5, Box 3099)
      On container, Gunsmoke "Don Matteo" Good Takes."
    - Extradition, open reel tape (Box 3099, Box 1102, Folder 15)
      On container, "Extradition part 1."
    - Extradition, open reel tape (Box 1103, Folder 2)
      On container, "GS Extradition-I-Steiner."
    - Extradition, 1963 November 11; 1 10" open reel audio tape (Box 3092)
    - Extradition, open reel tape (Box 1103, Folder 3)
      On container, "GS Extradition-II Steiner."
    - Extradition II, 1963 November 27; open reel tape (Box 1103, Folder 13, Box 3099)
      On container, "GS Extradition-II Steiner reel 1."
    - Far Places, open reel tape (Box 1065, Folder 11)
      On container, "Gunsmoke/"Far Places"."
    - Far Places, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1143, Folder 8)
      On container, "Gunsmoke 31229/The Far Places/ORIG 63."
    - Hard Virtue, Bad Seed, 1963; open reel tape (Box 1063, Folder 8)
      On container, "Gunsmoke/good takes/reel 4/"Hard Virtue"/"Bad Seed"."
    - Kate Heller, 1963 July 23; 1 10" open reel audio tape (Box 3099, Box 1065)
      On container, "F. Steiner."
    - Kate Heller, 1963 July 23; open reel tape (Box 1065, Folder 2)
      On container, "GS/Kate Heller/F. Steiner."
    - The Kite, 1964 February 7; open reel tape (Box 1063, Folder 1, Box 3099)
      On container, "CBS/"The Kite"/#7124/Roll#1."
    - The Kite, open reel tape (Box 1103, Folder 14)
      On container, "GS The Kite R.Shores."
    - Kitty Cornered, 1964 March 27; open reel tape (Box 1102, Folder 1, Box 3099)
      On container, "CBS. 7131 Gunsmoke 3-27-64 Kitty Conered Score."
    - Kitty Cornered, 1964 March 27; open reel tape (Box 1103, Folder 6)
      On container, "CBS 7131 score."
    - Lover Boy, 1963 August 23; open reel tape (Box 1065, Folder 8)
      On container, "G.S./"Lover Boy"/F.S. 2."
    - Lover boy, 1963 August 23; open reel tape (Box 1065, Folder 14)
      On container, "Gunsmoke/"Lover Boy"/F.S. 2."
    - Lyle's Kid, 1968 June 24; open reel audio tape (Box 931, Folder 5)
      On container, "CBS/6-24-68/Reel 12A/Log 192-211/Kid. Production no. 1310-1615-0307.
    - Lyle's Kid, 1968 June 28; open reel audio tape (Box 931, Folder 7)
      On container, "CBS/6-28-68/14A Log 236-245/Kid. Production no. 1310-1615-0302.
    - Lyle's Kid, 1968 June 28; open reel audio tape (Box 931, Folder 6)
      On container, "CBS/6-28-68/Reel 13B Log 212-235/Kid. Production no. 1310-1615-0307.
    - May Blossom, 1964 January 24; open reel tape (Box 1065, Folder 7)
      On container, "GS/May Blossom/T. Morgan."
    - May Blossom, 1964 January 24; open reel tape (Box 1065, Folder 9)
      On container, "GS/"May Blossom"/T. Morgan."
    - May Blossom, 1964 January 24; open reel tape (Box 1065, Folder 10)
    - My Sister's Keeper, 1963 October 11; open reel tape (Box 1103, Folder 9, Box 3099)
      On container, "GS My Sisters Keeper F.S. reel 2."
    - My Sister's Keeper, 1963 October 11; open reel tape (Box 1103, Folder 10)
      On container, "GS My Sisters Keeper F.S. reel 1."
    - No Chip, 1960 September 28; open reel tape (Box 1103, Folder 7, Box 3099)
      On container, "GSmoke "No Chip" #154-212 9/28/60."
    - Old Yellow Boots, 1961 August 4; open reel tape (Box 1063, Folder 10)
      On container, "G.S./"Old Yellow Boots"/reel 1."
    - Old Yellow Boots, 1961 August 4; open reel tape (Box 1063, Folder 11)
      On container, "Gunsmoke/"Old Yellow Boots"/reel 2."
    - Old Yellow Boots, 1961 August 4; open reel tape (Box 1063, Folder 12)
      On container, "G.S./#31005/"Old Yellow Boots"/roll 3."
    - Perce, open reel tape (Box 1063, Folder 2)
      On container, ""Perce"/L. Moraweck/ Reel 2."
    - Perce, 1961 August 17; open reel tape (Box 1063, Folder 19)
      On container, "G.S./#31004/"Perce/roll #1."
    - The Promotion, 1964 March 20; open reel tape (Box 1063, Folder 20)
      On container, "CBS/7129/Gunsmoke/"The Promotion"/reel #1."
    - The Quest for Asa Janin, 1963; open reel tape (Box 1065, Folder 12, Box 3099)
      On container, "G.S./"Asa Janin" (cont'd)."
    - The Quest for Asa Janin, open reel tape (Box 1103, Folder 4)
      On container, "GS "ASA JANIN"."
    - The River, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1154, Folder 2)
      On container, "Gunsmoke CBS #0560/"The River" Pt. 2/Reel 4 Music only."
    - The River, open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1154, Folder 3)
      On container, "Gunsmoke CBS #0560/"The River" Pt. 2/Reel 5 Music only."
    - Sharecroppers, 1974 October 2; open reel tape (Box 941, Folder 12)
      On container, "CTN/10-2-74/R59A/7 1/2 IPS/ADR - No Log #'s See Legend Inside/GS (CTR Only) "Sharecroppers"."
    - Shona, 1963; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1143, Folder 6)
      On container, "Gunsmoke #31220/"Shona"."
    - Tell Chester, 1963; open reel tape (Box 1063, Folder 4)
      On container, "Gunsmoke/#31231/"Tell Chester"/1963."
    - Tell Chester, 1963; open reel tape (Box 1063, Folder 5)
      On container, "Gunsmoke/#31231/"Tell Chester"/Playback Music."
    - Tell Chester, open reel tape (Box 1065, Folder 13)
      On container, "Gunsmoke/"Tell Chester"."
    - Unidentified, 1963 July 23; open reel tape (Box 1102, Folder 2)
      On container, "CBS-Gunsmoke Score_7102_Roll #2 7-23-63."
    - Unidentified, 1965 July 23; open reel tape (Box 1103, Folder 12)
      On container, "CBS-TV-Gunsmoke #7102-Score Roll #1, 7-23-65."
    - Logs 842-869, 1974 September 4; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1114, Folder 8)
      On container, "CTN/9-4-74/R44A/LOGS 842-869/GS - "Cibola Blanca Pt.2"."
    - Logs 870-890, 1974 September 4; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1114, Folder 9)
      On container, "CTN/9-4-74/R45A/LOGS 870-890/GS - "Cibola Blanca Pt.2"."
    - Logs 891-908, 1974 September 4; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1114, Folder 12)
      On container, "CTN/9-4-74/R46A/LOGS 891-908/GS "Perf Duty" (Libr.)."
    - Logs 793-816, 1974 August 23; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1114, Folder 20)
      On container, "CTN/8-23-74/R41A/LOGS 793-816/GS - "Dillon Must Die"."
    - Logs 363-372, 1973 August 24; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1120, Folder 1)
      On container, "CBS/8-24-73/R18A/LOGS 363/372/GS "Women - Pt.2" + Libr."
    - Logs 373-398, 1973 August 29; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1120, Folder 10)
      On container, "CBS/8-29-73/R19A/LOGS 373-398/GS "Child Between"."
    - Logs 399-417, 1973 August 29; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1120, Folder 15)
      On container, "CBS/8-29-73/R20A/LOGS 399-417/GS "Child Between"."
    - Logs 345-362, 1973 August 24; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1120, Folder 20)
      On container, "CBS/8-24-73/R17A/LOGS 345-362/GS "Women - Pt.2"."
    - Logs 599-613, 1974 August 6; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1134, Folder 9)
      On container, "CTN/8-6-74/R29A/LOGS 599-613/Print Takes Only/GS "Format"."
    - Logs 733-760, 1974 August 23; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1134, Folder 11)
      On container, "CTN/8-23-74/R37A/LOGS 733-760/GS "Tarnished Badge"."
    - Logs 665-647, 1974 August 14; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1134, Folder 14)
      On container, "CTN/8-7-74/R32A/LOGS 665-674/GS "Comancheros - Pt. 1" (Gtr)."
    - Logs 646-664, 1974 August 6; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1134, Folder 15)
      On container, "CTN/8-6-74/R31A/LOGS 646-664/GS "Comancheros - Pt. 1" H5O "Steal Now" (1Cue)."
    - Logs 761-775, 1974 August 23; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1134, Folder 16)
      On container, "CTN/8-23-74/R38A/LOGS 761-775/GS "Tarnished Badge" "Town In Chains"."
    - Logs 713-732, 1974 August 21; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1134, Folder 17)
      On container, "CTN/8-21-74/R36A/LOGS 713-732/GS "Dillon Must Die"."
    - Logs 710-712, 1974 August 16; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1134, Folder 18)
      On container, "CTN/8-16-74/R35A/LOGS 710-712/GS "Stringers" (Pno Cue)."
    - Logs 786-792, 1974 August 23; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1134, Folder 19)
      On container, "CTN/8-23-74/R40A/LOGS 786-792/GS "Performance Of Duty"."
    - Logs 2576-2568, 1975 March 7; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1137, Folder 11)
      On container, "CTN/3-7-75/R101 A/LOGS 2576-2568/GS "Manolo"."
    - Logs 2132-2575, 1975 March 7; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1140, Folder 5)
      On container, "CTN/3-7-75/R100A/LOGS 2132-2575/GS "Manolo"."
    - Trailers. Selections, 1/4 in. tape (Box 1142, Folder 6)
      On container, "Gunsmoke Trailers #3/Quest For Asa Jamin, Old York, Panacea Sikes, Ash, Shona, The Cousin, The Bad One, Renegades, Louie Pheeters, False Front, Old Comrade, Uncle Sunday, The Way It Is, The Hunger, Abe Elocker, Phoebe Strunk, The Ditch, Jenny, Root Down."
    - Logs 154-180, 1959 December 9; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1142, Folder 19)
      On container, Outtakes CBS 154-180 Gunsmoke/"Big Tom" Score/12-9-59."
    - Open reel and cassette tapes, 1980 [?] (Box 1833, Folder unknown container)
      Contains "Gunsmoke Theme"
    - Logs 13-33, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 1)
      On label "73/74 ... Circuit Judge" Side 1B.
    - Logs 34-36, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 2)
      On label "73/74 ... Circuit Judge" Side 2A.
    - Logs 37-46, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 2)
    - Logs 47-48, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 2)
      On label "73/74 ... Circuit Judge" Side 2B.
    - Log 344, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 3)
      On label "73/74 ... Women For Sale Pt 2" Side 19A.
    - Logs 345-348, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 3)
    - Logs 349-354, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 3)
      On label "73/74 ... Women For Sale Pt 2" Side 19B.
    - Logs 320-332, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 4)
      On label "73/74 ... Women For Sale Pt 2" Side 18A.
    - Logs 333-343, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 4)
      On label "73/74 ... Women For Sale Pt 2" Side 18B.
    - Logs 355-360, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 5)
      On label "73/74 ... Women For Sale Pt 2" Side 20A.
    - Logs 361-362, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 5)
      On label "73/74 ... Women For Sale Pt 2" Side 20B.
    - Logs 363-364, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 5)
    - Logs 1009-1019, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 6)
      On label "72/73 ... Patricia" Side 49A.
    - Logs 1020-1030, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 6)
      On label "72/73 ... Patricia" Side 49B.
    - Log 1037, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 7)
      On label "72/73 ... Patricia" Side 50A.
    - Logs 1031-1036, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 7)
    - Logs 728-735, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 9)
      On label "73/74 ... Kitty's Love Affair" Side 35A.
    - Logs 736-740, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 9)
    - Logs 741-747, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 9)
      On label "73/74 ... Kitty's Love Affair" Side 35B.
    - Logs 703-713, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 10)
      On label "73/74 ... Kitty's Love Affair" Side 34A.
    - Logs 714-727, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 10)
      On label "73/74 ... Kitty's Love Affair" Side 34B.
    - Logs 437-439, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 11)
      On label "73/74 ... Matt's Love Story" Side 22A.
    - Logs 440-442, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 11)
    - Logs 443-448, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 11)
      On label "73/74 ... Matt's Love Story" Side 22B.
    - Logs 453-455, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 11)
    - Logs 418-424, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 12)
      On label "73/74 ... Matt's Love Story" Side 21A.
    - Logs 425-436, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 12)
      On label "73/74 ... Matt's Love Story" Side 21B.
    - Logs 584-594, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 13)
      On label "72/73 ... Sarah" Side 28A.
    - Logs 595-602, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 13)
      On label "72/73 ... Sarah" Side 28B.
    - Logs 603-616, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 14)
      On label "72/73 ... Sarah" Side 29A.
    - Logs 617-637, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 14)
      On label "72/73 ... Sarah" Side 29B.
    - Logs 173-178, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 15)
      On label "74/75 ... The Wiving" Side 11A.
    - Logs 179-181, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 15)
      On label "74/75 ... The Wiving" Side 11B.
    - Logs 153-158, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 16)
      On label "74/75 ... The Wiving" Side 10A.
    - Logs 159-160, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 16)
    - Logs 161-172, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 16)
      On label "74/75 ... The Wiving" Side 10B.
    - Logs 128-138, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 17)
      On label "74/75 ... The Wiving" Side 9A.
    - Logs 139-152, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 17)
      On label "74/75 ... The Wiving" Side 9B.
    - Logs 174-184, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 18)
      On label "73/74 ... The Widow & The Rogue" Side 9A.
    - Logs 185-192, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 18)
      On label "73/74 ... The Widow & The Rogue" Side 9B.
    - Logs 193-198, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 19)
    - Logs 203-215, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 19)
      On label "73/74 ... The Widow & The Rogue" Side 10B.
    - Logs 216-226, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 20)
      On label "73/74 ... The Widow & The Rogue" Side 11A.
    - Logs 142-155, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 21)
      On label "73/74 ... Game of Death Part 1" Side 7A.
    - Logs 156-158, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 21)
      On label "73/74 ... Game of Death Part 1" Side 7B.
    - Logs 159-166, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 21)
    - Logs 167-173, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 22)
      On label "73/74 ... Game of Death Part 1" Side 8A.
    - Logs 120-123, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 23)
      On label "73/74 ... Game of Death Part 1 & 2" Side 6A.
    - Logs 124-127, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 23)
    - Logs 128-130, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 23)
    - Logs 131-141, 1 12" sound disc (Box 1842, Folder 23)
      On label "73/74 ... Game of Death Part 1" Side 6B.
    - Logs 266-289, 1971-1972; 1 12" sound disc (Box 3091)
    - Unidentified Contents, 1 10" open reel audio tape (Box 3092)
  - Have Gun Will Travel -- Recording Logs, Subseries 63.
    - Memories of Monica, 1962 October 1 (Box 1172, Folder 7)
      On cover, "The Black Bull / Prod. #1700-65 / F. Steiner / Memories of Monica / Prod. #1700-66 / October, 1962."
    - The Black Bull, 1962 October 1 (Box 1172, Folder 7)
  - Have Gun Will Travel -- Scores, Subseries 133.
    - Orchestral Scores, 1962 October 11; orchestral score (Box 19)
    - Billy Banjo (Episode Title), manuscript (Box 96)
      Full score.
      Score no. CPN5828.
    - Charles Red Dog (Episode Title), manuscript (Box 97)
      Score no. CPN5833.
    - Fragile (Episode Title), 1959 September 14; manuscript (Box 98)
      Score no. CPN5815
    - Hatchet Man (Episode Title) (Box 100)
      Score no. CPN5870.
    - Misguided Father (Episode Title), 1960 January; manuscript (Box 100)
      Show no. 0155-0108. Score no. CPN5867.
    - The Search (Episode Title), manuscript (Box 100)
      Score no. CPN5976.
    - Black Sheep (episode title), manuscript score (Box 101)
      Score no: CPN5898. Foreign Library: folders 2161-2170
    - Champagne Safari (Episode Title), manuscript score (Box 101)
      Score no: CPN5839. Foreign Library: folders 2131-2150
    - Have Gun Card (episode title), manuscript score (Box 101)
      Score no: CPN5843. Foreign Library: folders 2161-2170
    - Lady-Wall (episode title), manuscript score (Box 101)
      Score no: CPN5864. Foreign Library: folders 2211-2230
    - Laredo (episode title), manuscript score (Box 101)
    - Love of a Bad Woman (episode title), manuscript score (Box 101)
      Score no: CPN5889. Foreign Library: folders 2261-2270
    - Misguided Father (episode title)., manuscript score (Box 101)
      Score no: CPN5867. Foreign Library: folders 2231-2250
    - Stagecoach, The (episode title), manuscript score (Box 101)
      Score no: CPN5855. Foreign Library: folders 2241-2260
    - Love of a Bad Woman (episode title)., manuscript score (Box 102)
      Score no: CPN5889. Foreign Library: folders 2271-2280
    - Jonah and the Trout (Episode Title) (Box 107)
      Score no: CPN6009.
    - Coming of the Tiger (Episode Title) (Box 108)
      Score no: CPN6015.
    - Bandit, The (Episode Title) (Box 109)
      Score no: CPN6026.
    - Dreamgirl (Episode Title) (Box 109)
      Score no: CPN6025.
    - Hobson's Choice (Episode Title) (Box 109)
      Score no: CPN6027.
    - Hunt, The (Episode Title) (Box 109)
      Score no: CPN6023.
    - Mark of Cain (Episode Title) (Box 110)
      Score no: CPN6020.
    - Head of Hair (Episode Title) (Box 111)
      Score no: CPN5923.
    - Monte Bank (Episode Title) (Box 112)
      Score no: CPN5936.
    - Fog Bound (Episode Title) (Box 113)
      Score no: CPN5944.
    - Long Way Home (Episode Title) (Box 113)
      Score no: CPN5946.
    - Quiet Night in Town (Episode Title) (Box 113)
      Score no: CPN5951.
    - Every Man (Episode Title) (Box 114)
      Score no: CPN5962.
    - Gladiators (Episode Title) (Box 115)
      Score no: CPN5885.
    - International Affair (Episode Title) (Box 115)
      Score no: CPN5888.
    - Odds for Big Red (Episode Title) (Box 116)
      Score no: CPN5988.
    - Proof of Love (Episode Title) (Box 116)
      Score no: CPN5996.
    - Race, The (Episode Title) (Box 116)
      Score no: CPN5990.
    - Bear Bait (Episode Title) (Box 117)
      Score no: CPN5972.
    - Brother's Keeper (Episode Title) (Box 117)
      Score no: CPN5967.
    - Cure, The (Episode Title) (Box 117)
      Score no: CPN5965.
    - Last Judgement (Episode Title) (Box 117)
      Score no: CPN5970.
    - Education of Sarah Jane (Episode Title) (Box 118)
      Score no: CPN5983.
    - Knight to Remember (Episode Title) (Box 119)
      Score no: CPN5984.
    - Don't Shoot the Piano Player (Episode Title) (Box 122)
      Score no: CPN6029.
    - Kid, The (Episode Title) (Box 123)
      Score no: CPN5992.
    - Blind Circle (Episode Title) (Box 124)
      Score no: CPN6000.
    - Piano, The (Episode Title) (Box 124)
      Score no: CPN6002.
    - Bob Wire (Episode Title) (Box 126)
      Score no: CPN6066.
    - Caged at MacNab (Episode Title) (Box 126)
      Score no: CPN6068.
    - Unforgiving Minutes (Episode Title) (Box 126)
      Score no: CPN6067.
    - Black Bull (Episode Title) (Box 127)
      Score no: CPN6064.
    - Debutante (Episode Title) (Box 127)
      Score no: CPN6063.
    - Be Not Forgetful of Strangers (Episode Title) (Box 128)
      Score no: CPN6059.
    - Be Not Forgetfull of Strangers (Episode Title), 1962 October 11; orchestral score (Box 128)
    - Burning Tree (Episode Title), 1962 October 22; orchestral score (Box 128)
    - Burning Tree (Episode Title) (Box 128)
      Score no: CPN6061.
    - Marshall of Sweetwater (Episode Title) (Box 128)
      Score no: CPN6060.
    - Marshall of Sweetwater (Episode Title), 1962 October 15; orchestral score (Box 128)
    - Predators (Episode Title), 1962 October 8; orchestral score (Box 128)
    - Predators (Episode Title) (Box 128)
      Score no: CPN6058.
    - Treasure (Episode Title) (Box 128)
      Score no: CPN6062.
    - Treasure (Episode Title), 1962 October 25; orchestral score (Box 128)
    - Caravan, The (Episode Title) (Box 129)
      Score no: CPN6055.
    - Bird of Time (Episode Title) (Box 130)
      Score no: CPN6051.
    - Brotherhood (Episode Title) (Box 130)
      Score no: CPN6052.
    - Face of a Shadow (Episode Title) (Box 130)
      Score no: CPN6050.
    - Man in the Hour Glass (Episode Title) (Box 130)
      Score no: CPN6054.
    - Miracle of St. Francis (Episode Title) (Box 130)
      Score no: CPN6053.
    - Genesis Story (Episode Title) (Box 131)
      Score no: CPN6048.
    - Lady of the 5th Moon (Episode Title) (Box 133)
      Score no: CPN6082.
    - Walking Years (Episode Title) (Box 133)
      Score no: CPN6079.
    - Eve of St. Elmo (Episode Title) (Box 135)
      Score no: CPN6075.
    - Two Plus One (Episode Title) (Box 135)
      Score no: CPN6074.
    - American Primitive (Episode Title) (Box 136)
      Score no: CPN6073.
    - Gold Bar (Episode Title), manuscript; ozalid (Box 196)
      Score no: CPN5961.
    - Princess and the Gunfighters (Episode Title), manuscript; ozalid (Box 196)
      Score no: CPN5952.
    - Road, The (Episode Title), manuscript; ozalid (Box 196)
      Score no: CPN5966.
    - Seige (Episode Title), manuscript; ozalid (Box 196)
      Score no: CPN5974.
    - Uneasy Grave (Episode Title), manuscript; ozalid (Box 197)
      Score no: CPN5975.
  - Have Gun Will Travel -- Sound Recordings, Subseries 64.
    - Unidentified, open reel audio tape (Box 1060, Folder 2)
      On container, "HGWT/Scores/Reel VI."
    - Live Scores, open reel audio tape (Box 1060, Folder 3)
      On container, "HGWT/Live Scores/Reel V."
    - Man in an Hourglass, [1962]; open reel audio tape (Box 1060, Folder 19)
      On container, "HGWT/"Man In Hourglass"/Good Takes."
    - A Proof of Love, September 27, 1961; open reel audio tape (Box 1062, Folder 9)
      On container, "HGWT/#30962-M/"A Proof of Love"/2."
    - The Kid, September 14, 1961; open reel audio tape (Box 1062, Folder 10)
      On container, "HGWT/#30960-M/"The Kid"/9-14-61."
    - The Kid, September 14, 1961; open reel audio tape (Box 1062, Folder 11)
      On container, "HGWT/#30960-M/"The Kid"/2/9-14-1961."
    - Bob Wire, November 12, 1962; open reel audio tape (Box 1062, Folder 12)
      On container, "HGWT/"Bob Wire"/1875feet/Product #31174-M."
    - Montebank, November 7, 1960; open reel audio tape (Box 1062, Folder 13)
      On container, "HGWT/"Montebank"/all takes/11-7-60."
    - Odds For a Bid Red, August 28, 1961; open reel audio tape (Box 1062, Folder 14)
      On container, "HGWT/#30959/"Odds for Big Red"/1."
    - Odds For a Big Red, [1961]; open reel audio tape (Box 1062, Folder 15)
      On container, "HGWT/#30959/"Odds for Big Red"/2."
    - American Primitive, December 10, 1962; open reel audio tape (Box 1062, Folder 16)
      On container, "HGWT/"American Primitive"/31175."
    - Black Sheep, March 30, 1960; open reel audio tape (Box 1063, Folder 13)
      On container, "HGWT/"Black Sheep"/Moraweck/score."
    - Cage at McNaab, [1963]; open reel audio tape (Box 1063, Folder 14)
      On container, "HGWT/#31179/"Cage at McNaab"/good takes."
    - The Debutante, [1963]; open reel audio tape (Box 1063, Folder 15)
      On container, "H.G.W.T./#31169/"The Debutante"/good takes."
    - The Black Bull, [1963]; open reel audio tape (Box 1063, Folder 16)
      On container, "H.G.W.T./31165/"Black Bull"/good takes."
    - A Proof of Love, September 27, 1961; open reel audio tape (Box 1063, Folder 17)
      On container, "HGWT/#30962-M/"A Proof of Love"/1."
    - Everyman, February 1, 1961; 1/4 in. tape (Box 1142, Folder 15)
      On container, "HGWT/Everyman/Moraweck/2-1."
  - Hawaii Five-O -- Papers, Subseries 65.
    - Musical scores, undated (Box 1571)
    - Season 12, Episode 3: Though the Heavens Fall - score by Bruce Broughton and Morton Stevens, undated (Box 1591)
    - Show Report -- Music Operations (CBS Memorandum), 1977 October 3; 4 p. (Box 1859, Folder 11)